clickforbtc.com 2017-05-28

# Click For BTC | Earn Bitcoins - Bitcoin Advertising - Bitcoin PTC - Bitcoin Offerwall - Bitcoin Surveys › Privacy Policy

ClickForBTC is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy applies to the data collected by ClickForBTC through our website and services. Please, take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions regarding the matter.

Quick Links

1\. USERNAME   
2\. USER PASSWORDS   
3\. USER E-MAILS   
4\. COOKIES   
5\. ADVERTISEMENTS   
4\. PERSONAL

OTHER

PRIVACY POLICY QUESTIONS

1\. USERNAME

1.1. We may display your username within our site. However, to ensure your privacy, we will not needlessly expose it to the other people.

1.2. Your username will be displayed in our forum whenever you make a new post.

1.3. Your username can be displayed on different forums and social medias of ours if you have participated in one of our contest and have won one of the prizes.

2\. USER PASSWORDS

2.1. Your password will be stored in an irreversible format.

2.2. Your password will never be shown, sold or shared. Its sole purpose is to validate your ownership of your account.

3\. USER E-MAILS

3.1. Your e-mail address will never be shown, sold or shared!

3.2. Your personal e-mail address will only be used by ClickForBTC for communicating with you in regards to your support tickets, lost passwords, PIN recovery or some important official announcements.

3.3. Your Payment Processor e-mail address / account ID will only be used by ClickForBTC for receiving payments from you and sending them to you.

4\. COOKIES

4.1. Your browser must accept cookies.

4.2. Cookies will be used for storing your preferences.

4.3. Cookies can also be used for security purposes.

4.3. Cookies are used for storing "referral information" within the context of our affiliate program.

5\. ADVERTISEMENTS

5.1. ClickForBTC is not responsible for the content of the advertisements placed on our site. This includes, but is not limited to: user posts, advertisements and banner ads.

5.2. Clicking on an advertisement is your own responsibility. ClickForBTC is not liable for any problem/issue/damage caused by you visiting an advertisement or browsing the content of an advertiser.

5.3. All advertisements are the responsibility of the corresponding advertisers, and you must comply with their own Terms of Service and Privacy Policies.

5\. PERSONAL

6.1. ClickForBTC may collect some personal information from the users such as Full Name, Post Code, Year of Birth and Gender This information is only used to provide surveys trough our survey section

6.2. We might provide this information for the 3rd parties providing the surveys to our users.

6.3. Should you wish to delete your information we ask that you contact our support and we will honor your request. Do note however surveys will not be available then.

6.4. Pollfish Spesific Privacy Policy: “This website uses Pollfish web plugin. Pollfish is an on-line survey platform, through which, anyone may conduct surveys. Pollfish collaborates with Developers of applications for smartphones and website owners in order to have access to users of such applications/websites and address survey questionnaires to them. This website uses and enables Pollfish cookies. When a user connects to this website, Pollfish detects whether the user is eligible for a survey. Data collected by Pollfish will be associated with your answers to the questionnaires whenever Pollfish sents such questionnaires to eligible users. For a full list of data received by Pollfish through this website, please read carefully Pollfish respondent terms located at https://www.pollfish.com/terms/respondent. By using this website you accept this privacy policy document and you hereby give your explicit consent for the placement of a Pollfish cookie in your system and the processing by Pollfish of the aforementioned data. Furthermore, you are informed that you may disable Pollfish operation at any time by using the Pollfish “opt out section” available on Pollfish website or by disabling “third party cookies” from your browser’s settings. We once more invite you to check the Pollfish respondent’s terms of use, if you wish to have more detailed view of the way Pollfish works works. 

APPLE, GOOGLE AND AMAZON ARE NOT A SPONSOR NOR ARE INVOLVED IN ANY WAY IN THIS CONTEST/DRAW. NO APPLE PRODUCTS ARE BEING USED AS PRIZES.” 

PRIVACY POLICY QUESTIONS

If you have any questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy of ClickForBTC, please, don't hesitate to contact us!

### [Support](https://clickforbtc.freshdesk.com/)
